{
  "1": {
    "answer_false1": "I-19",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following ships had an on-board ice cream maker?",
    "answer_right": "Enterprise",
    "answer_false3": "Mikasa",
    "answer_false2": "Akashi",
    "id": 1
  },
  "2": {
    "answer_false1": "Skip bombing",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following refers to a naval tactic used by submarines?",
    "answer_right": "Wolfpacks",
    "answer_false3": "Outranging",
    "answer_false2": "Crossing the T",
    "id": 2
  },
  "3": {
    "answer_false1": "Ryuuhou",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following ships was converted from a cargo liner?",
    "answer_right": "Long Island",
    "answer_false3": "Langley",
    "answer_false2": "Chaser",
    "id": 3
  },
  "4": {
    "answer_false1": "Hiryuu",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following ships had the highest recorded speed?",
    "answer_right": "Maury",
    "answer_false3": "Haruna",
    "answer_false2": "Deutschland",
    "id": 4
  },
  "5": {
    "answer_false1": "Light cruiser",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Tashkent, the \"Blue Cruiser,\" was which type of ship?",
    "answer_right": "Destroyer",
    "answer_false3": "Battleship",
    "answer_false2": "Aircraft carrier",
    "id": 5
  },
  "6": {
    "answer_false1": "Enterprise",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following ships was awarded a total of 18 battle stars?",
    "answer_right": "San Diego",
    "answer_false3": "Portland",
    "answer_false2": "Saratoga",
    "id": 6
  },
  "7": {
    "answer_false1": "Nagato",
    "type": 1,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following battleships' main battery turrets had 4 barrels each?",
    "answer_right": "Richelieu",
    "answer_false3": "Littorio",
    "answer_false2": "Colorado",
    "id": 7
  },
  "8": {
    "answer_false1": "KÃ¶ln",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following ships is the teacher in the Lecture Hall?",
    "answer_right": "Amazon",
    "answer_false3": "Wichita",
    "answer_false2": "London",
    "id": 8
  },
  "9": {
    "answer_false1": "Suzuya",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following ships has animal ears?",
    "answer_right": "Takao",
    "answer_false3": "Kongou",
    "answer_false2": "Agano",
    "id": 9
  },
  "10": {
    "answer_false1": "Bache",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following ships has appeared on Juustagram?",
    "answer_right": "Amazon",
    "answer_false3": "Hermes",
    "answer_false2": "Honolulu",
    "id": 10
  },
  "11": {
    "answer_false1": "Z25",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following ships do NOT carry around a stuffed toy?",
    "answer_right": "Leipzig",
    "answer_false3": "Dido",
    "answer_false2": "Kiyonami",
    "id": 11
  },
  "12": {
    "answer_false1": "Manjuus",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which of the following are NOT always present on the Academy screen?",
    "answer_right": "Yuni",
    "answer_false3": "Shipgirls",
    "answer_false2": "Meowfficers",
    "id": 12
  },
  "13": {
    "answer_false1": "San Diego",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following ships has NOT yet received a retrofit?",
    "answer_right": "Benson",
    "answer_false3": "Cassin",
    "answer_false2": "Warspite",
    "id": 13
  },
  "14": {
    "answer_false1": "Potato",
    "type": 2,
    "wrong_time": 300,
    "question": "Which one of the following Meowfficers is NOT brown?",
    "answer_right": "Beer",
    "answer_false3": "Gral",
    "answer_false2": "Edelweiss",
    "id": 14
  },
  "all": [
    1,
    2,
    3,
    4,
    5,
    6,
    7,
    8,
    9,
    10,
    11,
    12,
    13,
    14
  ]
}